in today's world not all superheroes
wear capes meet vikas an ordinary man
with extraordinary responsibilities to
fulfill these responsibilities he has a
superpower
introducing ICICI prove protect and gain
a plan that empowers him to secure his
family's financial future and his dreams
it provides comprehensive protection to
his family including live cover
accidental death cover
[Music]
and accidental disability cover
vikas will get a lump sum on policy
maturity to fulfill his goals
and with easy documentation it is quite
simple to buy so let us see how this
plan works for example at 35 vikas pays
an annual premium of 62 603 rupees for
10 years for a policy term of 40 years
in case of his death during the policy
term his family will get a live cover of
50 lakh rupees and the policy will
terminate
in the event of an accidental death the
nominee will receive an additional cover
of 50 lakh rupees resulting in a total
benefit of one crore rupees consequently
the policy will terminate
in case of permanent disability due to
an accident he will get a lump sum of 50
lakh rupees and the policy benefits
continue
on Survival vikas will get Market linked
returns as a lump sum at the age of 75
to fulfill his dreams
this plan helps because to protect his
family financially in his absence
and also helps him secure his dreams for
a long and fulfilling life
be a pro like a superhero with ICICI
proof protect and Gain
[Music]
foreign